<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Erin Orstrom</title>
    <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Erin Orstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sidebar photo by Sacha Styles on Unsplash. Website © Erin Orstrom, {year}.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 13:52:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ErinOrstrom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You More Focused on Quality Results, or Seeing Your Employees&#39; Butts in Their Seats?</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/quality-results-vs-butts-in-seats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 13:52:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/quality-results-vs-butts-in-seats/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Kevin Bhagat on Unsplash
  There have been many folks posting recently around companies being compelled to let their employees work remotely due to the COVID-19 pandemic and how many of these employees self-report an increase in productivity and overall job satisfaction. This has got me thinking about a topic that really bugs me as it relates to the mindsets of many companies and leaders, specifically in America, today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Converted My Existing Website to Use Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/converting-site-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 22:11:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/converting-site-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write this post as a guide on how I converted my website to use Hugo, a static site generator, in order to host blog posts without using a CMS like WordPress. When I was looking for resources and guides on how to build a Hugo site, nearly every resource I ran across was a guide on how to build a Hugo site from scratch. Which is great because that&amp;rsquo;s where most people start from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Film Festival</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nashville-film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 12:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nashville-film-festival/</guid>
      <description>A volunteer project I am currently involved with, working with web developers to update the design of the Nashville Film Festival website to better align with their brand and mission, in addition to updating the site security.
We meet once a week for progress updates. We have secured the new design approval based on wireframes the team created. We are currently at the beginning of the implementation stage of the redesign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Developer Toolbox Podcast</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/junior-developer-toolbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 19:31:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/junior-developer-toolbox/</guid>
      <description>Junior Developer Toolbox was a podcast about building, maintaining, and surviving a career in software engineering. We provided real talk from the trenches about everyday life as a junior developer.
The podcast was co-hosted by my friend Dave Harned and myself, and early on by Jason Belcher. We produced 40 episodes over 18 months on a biweekly basis on various topics related to software development and our experience working in the industry as junior software developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Software School Cohort 12 Class Website</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nss-class-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:48:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nss-class-website/</guid>
      <description>Github repo: https://github.com/nss-day-cohort-12/nss12-class-website
Purpose: Create a class website for NSS cohort 12 to showcase school work to potential employers before Demo Day.
My Contributions: Initial repo and site setup, helped construct individual modals, group photo swap behavior, and overall project organization.
Description: I was team lead on the creation of our class website. I coordinated the project&amp;rsquo;s parts to ensure each part was completed and merged with the whole project successfully and saw the project through from vision to completed product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for A New Adventure</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/time-for-a-new-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 21:51:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/time-for-a-new-adventure/</guid>
      <description>This blog post has been a long time coming! I have been meaning to revamp my website by giving it a new design and ability to host blog posts for over a year now. After Dave and I stopped producing the Junior Developer Toolbox podcast, I knew I still had more to say and wanted to continue to help others along their journey. But there are also other topics I have thoughts and ideas to get out into the world - general career, travel, and dating being just a few examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Bootcamp? Or Not To Bootcamp? Deep Dive into Erin&#39;s NSS Experience</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/to-bootcamp-or-not-to-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/to-bootcamp-or-not-to-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>There won&amp;rsquo;t be a new episode of Junior Developer Toolbox this week. But fret not! Dave and I are taking a break to recharge and plan upcoming show content. Dave is soaking up some rays on a cruise with his family (I&amp;rsquo;m jealous), but we wanted to make sure our listeners still received some great content this week. So I wrote this blog post to accompany the series on software bootcamps we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on recently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Time at BarCamp Nashville 2017</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/this-one-time-at-barcamp-nashville-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 20:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/post/this-one-time-at-barcamp-nashville-2017/</guid>
      <description>Hello All! We&amp;rsquo;re working hard to get our third episode (Episode 2) edited and finalized to release. In the meantime, we&amp;rsquo;d like to share our experience from BarCamp Nashville 2017 this past weekend.
Erin, Dave, and Jason finally got together in person for the first time at the BarCamp Nashville 2017 Conference, which was hosted at Nashville Software School this year. BarCamp Nashville is a free, annual &amp;ldquo;unconference&amp;rdquo; that brings together the local tech community to explore, share and connect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>