<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>software bootcamp on Erin Orstrom</title>
    <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/tags/software-bootcamp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in software bootcamp on Erin Orstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:09:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ErinOrstrom.com/tags/software-bootcamp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To Bootcamp? Or Not To Bootcamp? Deep Dive into Erin&#39;s NSS Experience</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/blog/2019-03/to-bootcamp-or-not-to-bootcamp-deep-dive-into-erins-nss-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/blog/2019-03/to-bootcamp-or-not-to-bootcamp-deep-dive-into-erins-nss-experience/</guid>
      <description>There won&amp;rsquo;t be a new episode of Junior Developer Toolbox this week. But fret not! Dave and I are taking a break to recharge and plan upcoming show content. Dave is soaking up some rays on a cruise with his family (I&amp;rsquo;m jealous), but we wanted to make sure our listeners still received some great content this week. So I wrote this blog post to accompany the series on software bootcamps we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on recently.
Over the last few episodes, we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about factors to consider when determining whether a software development bootcamp is the best choice for your situation (Episode 34), how to stay encouraged through the &amp;ldquo;pit of despair&amp;rdquo; during the program (Episode 35), what the job search is like after completing a bootcamp program (Episode 36), and everything in between. I want to share my decision making process and also mention some things I wish I had known, or planned better for before enrolling in Nashville Software School, my NSS bootcamp experience, and what my job search post NSS graduation was like.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to the show for a while, you know that I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to college for software development/computer science. I stumbled upon it about a year into my first job after college and started learning from free online resources for a few months before attending meetups where others introduced me to Nashville Software School and the concept of a software bootcamp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>