<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Erin Orstrom</title>
    <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Erin Orstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sidebar photo by Sacha Styles on Unsplash. Website © Erin Orstrom, {year}.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 12:50:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Film Festival</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nashville-film-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 12:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nashville-film-festival/</guid>
      <description>A volunteer project I am currently involved with, working with web developers to update the design of the Nashville Film Festival website to better align with their brand and mission, in addition to updating the site security.
We meet once a week for progress updates. We have secured the new design approval based on wireframes the team created. We are currently at the beginning of the implementation stage of the redesign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Developer Toolbox Podcast</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/junior-developer-toolbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 19:31:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/junior-developer-toolbox/</guid>
      <description>Junior Developer Toolbox was a podcast about building, maintaining, and surviving a career in software engineering. We provided real talk from the trenches about everyday life as a junior developer.
The podcast was co-hosted by my friend Dave Harnedand myself, and early on by Jason Belcher. We produced 40 episodes over 18 months on a biweekly basis on various topics related to software development and our experience working in the industry as junior software developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Software School Cohort 12 Class Website</title>
      <link>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nss-class-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:48:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ErinOrstrom.com/portfolio/nss-class-website/</guid>
      <description>Github repo: https://github.com/nss-day-cohort-12/nss12-class-website
Purpose: Create a class website for NSS cohort 12 to showcase school work to potential employers before Demo Day.
My Contributions: Initial repo and site setup, helped construct individual modals, group photo swap behavior, and overall project organization.
Description: I was team lead on the creation of our class website. I coordinated the project&amp;rsquo;s parts to ensure each part was completed and merged with the whole project successfully and saw the project through from vision to completed product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>